<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipe app</string>
    <!-- Title, Ingredients and Instruction of veg foods  -->
    <string name="veg_rec_aloo_gobi">Aloo Gobi</string>
    <string name="veg_rec_dal_makhani">Dal Makhani</string>
    <string name="veg_rec_paneer_butter_masala">Paneer Butter Masala</string>
    <string name="veg_rec_matar_paneer">Matar Paneer</string>
    <string name="ingre_aloo_gobi"> ● 1 medium cauliflower, cut into florets ● 2 medium potatoes, peeled and cubed ● 1 tablespoon vegetable oil ● 1 teaspoon cumin seeds ● 1 onion, chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon coriander powder ● 1 teaspoon garam masala ● 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder ● Salt to taste </string>
    <string name="ingre_dal_makhani"> ● 1 cup black lentils, soaked overnight ● 1 cup kidney beans, soaked overnight ● 1 tablespoon vegetable oil ● 1 onion, chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon garam masala ● 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder ● 1/4 cup heavy cream ● Salt to taste </string>
    <string name="ingre_paneer_butter_masala"> ● 14 ounces paneer cheese, cut into cubes ● 1 tablespoon vegetable oil ● 1 onion, chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon garam masala ● 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder ● 1 (14-ounce) can diced tomatoes ● 1 (14-ounce) can coconut milk ● 1/4 cup heavy cream ● Salt to taste </string>
    <string name="ingre_matar_paneer"> ● 1 cup frozen peas ● 1 pound paneer cheese, cut into cubes ● 1 tablespoon vegetable oil ● 1 onion, chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon coriander powder ● 1/2 teaspoon cumin powder ● 1/4 teaspoon garam masala ● 1/2 teaspoon salt ● 1/4 cup chopped cilantro </string>
    <string name="instruction_aloo_gobi"> 1. Heat the oil in a large skillet over medium heat. Add the cumin seeds and cook until fragrant, about 30 seconds. 2. Add the onion and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 3. Add the garlic, ginger, turmeric powder, coriander powder, garam masala, and red chili powder. Cook for 1 minute, stirring constantly. 4. Add the potatoes and cauliflower. Stir to coat with the spices. 5. Add 1 cup of water. Bring to a boil, then reduce heat and simmer until the potatoes and cauliflower are tender, about 15 minutes. 6. Season with salt to taste. Serve hot with rice or roti. </string>
    <string name="instruction_dal_makhani"> 1. Drain and rinse the lentils and kidney beans. 2. Heat the oil in a large pot over medium heat. Add the onion and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 3. Add the garlic, ginger, turmeric powder, garam masala, and red chili powder. Cook for 1 minute, stirring constantly. 4. Add the lentils and kidney beans. Cover with water and bring to a boil. 5. Reduce heat and simmer until the lentils and kidney beans are tender, about 1 hour. 6. Stir in the heavy cream. Season with salt to taste. Serve hot with rice or naan. </string>
    <string name="instruction_butter_masala"> 1. Heat the oil in a large skillet over medium heat. Add the onion and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 2. Add the garlic, ginger, turmeric powder, garam masala, and red chili powder. Cook for 1 minute, stirring constantly. 3. Add the diced tomatoes and cook until heated through, about 5 minutes. 4. Stir in the coconut milk. Bring to a simmer, then reduce heat and simmer for 10 minutes. 5. Add the paneer cheese and cook until heated through, about 2 minutes. 6. Stir in the heavy cream. Season with salt to taste. Serve hot with rice or naan. </string>
    <string name="instruction_matar_paneer"> 1. Heat the oil in a large skillet over medium heat. 2. Add the onion and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 3. Add the garlic, ginger, turmeric powder, coriander powder, cumin powder, and garam masala and cook for 1 minute, stirring constantly. 4. Add the peas and paneer cheese and cook for 5 minutes, stirring occasionally. 5. Add the salt and 1/4 cup of water. 6. Bring to a boil, then reduce heat and simmer for 10 minutes. 7. Stir in the cilantro and serve. </string>
    <!-- Title, Ingredients and Instruction of non veg foods  -->
    <string name="non_rec_butter_chicken">Butter Chicken</string>
    <string name="non_rec_chicken_tikka">Chicken Tikka Masala</string>
    <string name="non_rec_fish_tikka">Fish Tikka Masala</string>
    <string name="non_rec_fish_pakoda">Fish Pakoras</string>
    <string name="ingre_butter_chicken"> ● 1 kg bone-in chicken thighs, cut into 1-inch pieces ● 1/2 cup plain yogurt ● 1 tablespoon lemon juice ● 1 tablespoon garam masala ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste ● 1/2 teaspoon salt ● 1/4 teaspoon black pepper ● 2 tablespoons butter ● 1 onion, finely chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 (14-ounce) can diced tomatoes ● 1/2 cup heavy cream ● 1 tablespoon kasoori methi (dried fenugreek leaves) </string>
    <string name="ingre_chicken_tikka"> ● 1 kg bone-in chicken thighs, cut into 1-inch pieces ● 1/2 cup plain yogurt ● 1 tablespoon lemon juice ● 1 tablespoon garam masala ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste ● 1/2 teaspoon salt ● 1/4 teaspoon black pepper ● 2 tablespoons butter ● 1 onion, finely chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 tablespoon ginger, minced ● 1 (14-ounce) can diced tomatoes ● 1/2 cup heavy cream ● 1 tablespoon kasoori methi (dried fenugreek leaves) </string>
    <string name="ingre_fish_tikka"> ● 1 pound fish fillets, cut into 1-inch pieces ● 1/2 cup plain yogurt ● 1 tablespoon lemon juice ● 1 teaspoon garam masala ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon paprika ● 1/2 teaspoon salt ● 1/4 teaspoon black pepper ● 2 tablespoons vegetable oil ● 1 onion, chopped ● 2 cloves garlic, minced ● 1 (14-ounce) can diced tomatoes ● 1 (14-ounce) can coconut milk ● 1 tablespoon chopped cilantro </string>
    <string name="ingre_fish_pakoda"> ● 1 pound fish fillets, cut into 1-inch pieces ● 1 cup chickpea flour ● 1 teaspoon turmeric powder ● 1 teaspoon garam masala ● 1/2 teaspoon salt ● 1/4 teaspoon black pepper ● 1/4 cup chopped cilantro ● 1/4 cup chopped onion ● 1 cup water ● Vegetable oil for frying </string>
    <string name="instruction_butter_chicken"> 1. In a large bowl, combine the chicken, yogurt, lemon juice, garam masala, turmeric powder, ginger-garlic paste, salt, and pepper. Marinate for at least 30 minutes, or up to overnight. 2. Heat the butter in a large skillet over medium heat. Add the onion, garlic, and ginger and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 3. Add the marinated chicken and cook until browned on all sides, about 5 minutes. 4. Stir in the diced tomatoes and bring to a simmer. Reduce heat to low and simmer for 20 minutes, or until the chicken is cooked through. 5. Stir in the heavy cream and kasoori methi. Serve hot with basmati rice or naan. </string>
    <string name="instruction_chicken_tikka"> 1. In a large bowl, combine the chicken, yogurt, lemon juice, garam masala, turmeric powder, ginger-garlic paste, salt, and pepper. Marinate for at least 30 minutes, or up to overnight. 2. Thread the chicken onto skewers. 3. Preheat a grill or grill pan to medium heat. Grill the chicken for 5-7 minutes per side, or until cooked through. 4. While the chicken is cooking, heat the butter in a large skillet over medium heat. Add the onion, garlic, and ginger and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. 5. Add the diced tomatoes and bring to a simmer. Reduce heat to low and simmer for 20 minutes, or until the sauce has thickened. 6. Stir in the heavy cream and kasoori methi. 7. Serve the chicken tikka masala over basmati rice or naan. </string>
    <string name="instruction_fish_tikka"> 1. In a large bowl, combine fish, yogurt, lemon juice, garam masala, turmeric powder, paprika, salt, and pepper. Marinate for at least 30 minutes. 2. Heat oil in a large skillet over medium heat. Add onion and cook until softened, about 5 minutes. Add garlic and cook for 1 minute more. 3. Add diced tomatoes, coconut milk, and fish marinade. Bring to a simmer and cook for 10 minutes, or until fish is cooked through. 4. Stir in cilantro and serve immediately. </string>
    <string name="instruction_fish_pakoda"> 1. In a large bowl, combine chickpea flour, turmeric powder, garam masala, salt, pepper, cilantro, and onion. 2. Add water and whisk until smooth. 3. Dip fish pieces in batter and coat well. 4. Heat oil in a large pot or deep fryer to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). 5. Fry fish pieces in batches until golden brown and cooked through, about 3-4 minutes per batch. 6. Drain on paper towels and serve immediately. </string>
    <!-- Title, Ingredients and Instruction of sweets  -->
    <string name="sweets_coconut_laddu">Coconut Laddoo</string>
    <string name="sweets_banana_cake">Eggless Banana Cake</string>
    <string name="sweets_kalakand">Kalakand</string>
    <string name="sweets_rose_milk">Rose Milk</string>
    <string name="ingre_coconut_laddu"> 1. 1 tin Nestlé MILKMAID 2. 100 gms Milk Powder 3. 5 cups (350 gms) Fresh Grated Coco </string>
    <string name="ingre_banana_cake"> 1. 1/2 tin Nestlé MILKMAID 2. 1/2 cup (75 gms) Nestlé a+ Nourish Dahi (Curd) 3. 50 gms Softened Butter 4. 2 cups (200gms) Maida (All Purpose Flour) 5. 1 tsp Baking Powder 6. 1/2 tsp Baking Soda 7. 2 Mashed Bananas 8. 1 tsp Vanilla Essence </string>
    <string name="ingre_kalakand"> 1. 1/2 tin Nestlé MILKMAID 2. 500 ml Nestlé a+ Toned Milk 3. 500 ml Water 4. 5 tbsp Rose Syrup 5. 12 Crushed Ice Cubes </string>
    <string name="ingre_rose_milk"> 1. 1 tin Nestlé MILKMAID 2. 2 heaped tbsp Nestlé Everyday Dairy Whitener 3. 500 gms Paneer 4. 3-4 Powdered Elaichi 5. 1 Silver Leaf </string>
    <string name="instruction_coconut_laddu"> 1. Keep aside 1 cup of the grated coconut. Put Nestlé MILKMAID, milk powder, and remaining grated coconut into a thick bottomed pan and mix well. Heat the mixture, stirring constantly, so that it does not stick to the bottom of the pan. 2. Switch the flame to low and cook until the mixture starts leaving the sides of the pan (approx. 5 minutes). Remove from the flame and let it cool. 3. Once cooled, take small portions and roll them into laddus using oiled hands. Then, roll the laddus in the reserved grated coconut. The laddus are now ready to be served. </string>
    <string name="instruction_banana_cake"> 1. Preheat the oven to 180o C. Grease a cake pan, dust it with maida and keep aside. Beat together softened butter and Nestlé MILKMAID till it is creamy. Add dahi and whisk well. 2. Sieve together maida, baking powder and baking soda. Fold it into the Milkmaid mixture, add mashed bananas and mix well. Add the vanilla essence. 3. Pour into the prepared cake pan and bake in the preheated oven for 25 –30 minutes, or until a toothpick inserted comes out clean. Cool for 5 minutes and remove onto a serving dish. Slice and serve. </string>
    <string name="instruction_kalakand"> 1. Mash paneer coarsely and mix in Everyday Dairy Whitener and Nestlé MILKMAID. 2. Heat the mixture in a thick bottom pan. Cook on medium heat with constant stirring till the mixture becomes thick and starts leaving the sides of the pan. 3. Remove from the fire and spread onto a greased plate. Sprinkle elaichi powder. 4. Top with silver leaf. 5. Cool and cut into squares. </string>
    <string name="instruction_rose_milk"> 1. Mix Nestlé MILKMAID, milk, and water. 2. Add the rose syrup and crushed ice cubes. 3. Serve chilled! </string>
</resources>